partymart.com 2017-02-03

# Privacy Policy

Updated: Monday October 31st, 2011

Effective: Tuesday November 1st, 2011

PartyMart.com respects your privacy. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. The information that you provide us with will be kept confidential and will only be used to support your customer relationship with PartyMart.com. Information we request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, credit card details, customer preference information, as well as other similar or relevant personal information.

We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you. This refers to our ability to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share news regarding products, service and company offerings with you.

We do not sell your personal information. At any time you may contact PartyMart.com with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You may also ask at any time to view the personal data you have given us and request a correction or deletion of your personal information. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by using enhanced encryption technology provided by our SSL security certificate.

THIRD PARTIES

PartyMart.com will not sell, trade, or rent your information to others. Personal information, such as your name, address and phone number or information regarding your order and the products you have purchased, will not be sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent.

Please be aware that other websites accessed through PartMart.com may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third party websites linked to or from PartyMart.com are not covered by this privacy statement. PartyMart.com reserves all rights herein and is not responsible for any actions of a third party.

Please note that while it is PartyMart.com’s intention to protect and not disclose personal information we will abide by all governing and legal rulings including legal requests from various governments and law-enforcement officials where necessary.  This process may also include pro-active protection of PartyMart.com, its customers, employees and properties where necessary at the managements sole discretion.

This policy was last updated on October 31st, 2011 and effective on the same date. If and hwen this policy is changed the dates will automatically be updated, no further notification may be made.
